manrepeller.com 2019-05-06

# Privacy Policy - Man Repeller

Thanks for visiting! ManRepeller.com (referred to below as “the Website”) has prepared this privacy policy to explain how we collect, use, and share information and personal data in accordance with applicable data protection and privacy laws. By using the Website, you consent to such collection, use and sharing of your information and Personal Data and agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy. The Website does not knowingly collect or solicit personal information from persons under thirteen years of age. If you are under 13, please do not attempt to register for Website or send any information about yourself to us, including your name, address, telephone number, or email address. No one under age 13 may provide any personal information to or on Website.

Any paid collaborations or sponsorships are disclosed within the respective editorial. We are also a participant in the Amazon Services LLC Associates Program, an affiliate advertising program designed to provide a means for us to earn fees by linking to Amazon.com and affiliated sites. We also periodically monetize outbound product links via SkimLinks, rewardStyle, and other such services. You are encouraged to consult their respective policies available at:  
<https://www.rewardstyle.com/privacy>  
<https://skimlinks.com/privacy-policy>

In addition to the use of cookies described in this policy, such third party affiliate service providers may use certain tracking technology, such as deep linking or device fingerprinting to leverage and improve functionality across sites and apps and to better understand who visits the Website and the frequency and interval of such visits. You are responsible for all of your activity in connection with the Website and accessing the Website. Man Repeller is not responsible for the content of linked sites.

 **A. Information We Collect Automatically**  
The Website and our third-party partners (including any third-party content, advertising, and analytics providers) automatically collect certain information from your device or web browser when you interact with the Website to help us understand how our users use the Website and to target advertising to you (which we will refer to in this Privacy Policy collectively as “Usage Data”). For example, each time you visit the Website we and our third-party service providers automatically collect your IP address, mobile device identifier or other unique identifier, browser and computer type, access time, the Web page you came from, the URL you go to next, the Web page(s) that you access during your visit and your interaction with content or advertising on the Website.

We and our third-party partners use this data for a variety of purposes including: to diagnose problems with our servers and software, to administer the Website, to gather demographic information and to target advertising to you on the Website and elsewhere online. The Usage Data we collect is generally non-identifying, but if we associate it with you as a specific and identifiable person, we will treat it as Personal Data.

 **B. EU Personal Data Request**  
If you are a resident of the European Economic Area (EEA), you have the right to: (1) request access to your Personal Data and rectification of inaccurate Personal Data; (2) request erasure of your Personal Data; (3) request restrictions on the processing of your Personal Data; (4) object to processing your Personal Data; and/or (5) the right to data portability (“collectively, “Requests”). We can only process Requests from a user whose identity has been verified. To verify your identity, please provide your email address or [URL] when you make a request. You can submit a request emailing privacy@manrepeller.com and stating, “I am an EU resident and would like to exercise my individual rights” option. You also have the right to lodge a complaint with a supervisory authority.

 **C. Retaining, Modifying and Deleting Your Personal Data**  
You may access the information we hold about you. If you wish to exercise this right, please contact us using privacy@manrepeller.com If you would like to update, correct, modify or delete from our database any Personal Data you previously submitted to us, please let us know by accessing and updating your profile. If you delete certain information you may not be able to order services in the future without re-submitting such information. We will comply with your request as soon as reasonably practicable. Also, please note that we will maintain Personal Data in our database whenever we are required to do so by law.

Please note that we need to retain certain information for record keeping purposes and/or to complete any transactions that you began prior to requesting such change or deletion (for example, when you enter a promotion, you may not be able to change or delete the Personal Data provided until after the completion of such promotion). We will retain your Personal Data for the period necessary to fulfill the purposes outlined in this Policy unless a longer retention period is required or permitted by law.

 **D. Cookie Policy**  
We use tracking technologies, such as cookies and local storage.

1\. Cookies and Local Storage  
Cookies and local storage may be set and accessed on your computer. Upon your first visit to the Website, a cookie or local storage will be sent to your computer that uniquely identifies your browser. “Cookies” and local storage are small files containing a string of characters that is sent to your computer’s browser and stored on your device when you visit a website. Many major Web services use cookies to provide useful features for their users. Each Web site can send its own cookie to your browser. Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. You can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent; however, if you reject cookies, you will not be able to sign in to parts of the Website or take full advantage of our Website.

Our Services use the following types of cookies for the purposes set out below:

Category of Use: Functionality Cookies  
Purpose: We use cookies to ensure our site runs properly. It allows us serve content, have features such as slideshows and commenting, and display ads.

Category of Use: Analytics and Performance Cookies  
Purpose: We use analytics and performance cookies to measure site growth, understand behavior patterns, and any difficulties with the site at an aggregate level. We use this data to create better content and experience for our readers through site improvements and updates.

Category of Use: Targeted and Advertising Cookies  
Purpose: We, our advertising partners, ad networks, or social platforms may use cookies to display ads, track performance of advertisements, or for retargeting purposes.

2\. Third Party Services and Cookies  
Partners and affiliate services may also use cookies in connection with your device or browser. These cookies are dropped on devices or browsers so that such third parties can monetize outbound links, visits and other actions.

 **E. Sensitive Personal Data**  
Subject to the following paragraph, we ask that you not send us, and you not disclose, any sensitive personal data as this term is defined under applicable data protection and privacy laws (for example, social security numbers, information related to racial or ethnic origin, political opinions, religion or other beliefs, health, biometrics or genetic characteristics, criminal background or trade union membership) on or through the Website or otherwise to us.

If you send or disclose any sensitive personal data to us, you consent to our processing and use of such sensitive personal data in accordance with this Privacy Policy. If you do not consent to our processing and use of such sensitive personal data, you must not submit such content to our Website.

 **F. Information Sharing Practices**  
(1) Generally. We share Non-Personal Data, including Usage Data, de-identified Personal Data and aggregated user statistics, with third parties in our discretion. We share User Information, including Personal Data, as otherwise described in this Policy, and under the following circumstances:  
(2) Service Providers. From time to time, we enter into relationships with third parties who provide services to us (for example, analytics companies, advertisers and ad agencies, data management and storage services or credit card processing services, sweepstakes or contest prize fulfillment).  
(3) Third-Party Marketing. If you are a resident of the European Economic Area, you will have a choice (opt-in or opt-out) before we share your information with third parties for marketing purposes. Otherwise, we share your information (including Personal Data) with third parties for those third parties’ own direct marketing purposes.  
(4) Change of Control. In the event we go through a business transition (such as a merger, acquisition by another company, bankruptcy, or sale of all or a portion of our assets, including, without limitation, during the course of any due diligence process), your Personal Data will likely be among the assets transferred. By providing your Personal Data, you agree that we can transfer such information in those circumstances without your further consent. Should such a business transition occur, we will make reasonable efforts to request that the new owner or combined entity (as applicable) follow this Privacy Policy with respect to your Personal Data. If your Personal Data would be used contrary to this Privacy Policy, we will request that you receive prior notice.  
(5) Other Disclosure Scenarios. We reserve the right, and you hereby expressly authorize us, to share User Information: (i) in response to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish, protect, or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims; (ii) if we believe it is necessary in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, fraud, or situations involving potential threats to the safety of any person or property; (iii) if we believe it is necessary to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding significant abuse of the Website infrastructure or the Internet in general (such as voluminous spamming, denial of service attacks, or attempts to compromise the security of information); (iv) to protect and defend our legal rights or property, our services or their users, or any other party, and to protect the health and safety of our users or the general public; and (v) to our parent company, subsidiaries, joint ventures, or other companies under common control with us (in which case we will require such entities to honor this Privacy Policy).
